loomly.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy | Loomly

Last updated: May 24, 2018

Calendy, Inc ("us", "we", "our" or “Loomly.com”) operates the [Loomly.com](https://www.loomly.com/) website (the "Service"). 

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information, Account Information and Log Information when you use our Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service, and when you agree, to contact you with additional information and offers related to the Service. By signing up to use our Service, and opting-in to our uses of your information, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy (the “Privacy Policy”). Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at <https://www.loomly.com/terms>

When you sign-up for our Service, and while using our Service, you may provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information includes your name, your company or business’s name, a description of your company, your email address, and your postal address ("Personal Information"). 

When you sign-up for our Service, and while using our Service, you may also provide us with information about the subscription you choose, such as the plan, billing method and the effective dates of your subscription (“Plan Information”) and information connected with the use of our Service, such as the name of the calendars you create, the names and emails of the other users you invite to collaborate with you, any information you have made available by linking your social media accounts (ID, URL, name, profile picture of the account, and all analytics Loomly.com is able to collect pursuant to each social media company’s terms of use), any content you input (whether media or copy), any criteria you select (i.e. audience targeting, budget, etc.), and any dates you schedule (“Content Information,” and collectively with Plan Information the “Account Information”). 

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other data generated from cookies (see the Cookies section below for more information). 

We collect Personal Information and Plan Information for the purpose of providing the Service, identifying and communicating with you, responding to your requests/inquiries, servicing your account, improving our services, and to the extent you have not opted-out, contacting you with information about our Services and offers. We will only retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of our legitimate business interests and satisfying any legal or reporting requirements. 

We collect Content Information and Log Information for the purpose of providing and improving the Service, and to advertise to you through re-remarketers. 

We may link or combine the Personal Information we collect and/or receive about you and the Log Data and Account Data we collect automatically during your visit to our website. This allows us to provide you with a personalised experience that improves our Service. 

Loomly.com engages certain third parties that may process data submitted to Loomly.com to perform certain business-related functions and to increase our Service's functionality. These companies assist with processing your payment, monitoring and analyzing how our Service is used and other services. When we engage another company to perform such functions, we may provide them with information, including Personal Information, Log Data and Account Information, in connection with their performance of such functions. These subprocessors are listed below, as may be updated by Loomly.com from time to time: 

  * Amazon Web Services, Inc. 
  * Intercom, Inc. 
  * Attribution Inc. 
  * Stripe, Inc. 
  * The Rocket Science Group LLC  dba MailChimp 
  * OneSignal, Inc. 
  * Google Inc. (Google Analytics and GSuite) 
  * Mailgun Technologies, Inc. 
  * Bugsnag Inc. 
  * New Relic, Inc. 

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform specific tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your information for any other purpose. These third parties may analyze the data we provide, combine that data with publicly available data, and provide us with access to their analysis and reports. 

Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and transferred to your device. We use cookies to collect information in order to improve our services for you. The third-parties we work with may also use cookies to help us analyze how our users are using the Service. 

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. The Help feature on most browsers provide information on how to accept cookies, disable cookies or to notify you when receiving a new cookie. 

If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of our Service and we recommend that you leave them turned on. 

Our site integrates with your social media accounts. These integration features may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are hosted on our site or by a third party, and your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

Loomly.com uses Google AdWords, Facebook Ads, Twitter Ads, LinkedIn Ads, AdRoll, Criteo, Outbrain, and Taboola to advertise on third-party web sites to you after you visited our Service. We, and our third-party vendors, use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service. 

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc. 

You can customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: <https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated>

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> \- for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. 

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such messages from us, you will be able to tell us by selecting certain boxes on forms we use when we first collect your contact details. You may also opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by updating your preferences from your account page or following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us. 

Our Website facilitates the publishing of your posts on various social media account and may include publicly accessible blogs or community forums. Any information you post onto your social media accounts or provide in our blog/forum areas may be read, collected and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, please [contact us](mailto:contact@loomly.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. In the event you wish to remove information from your social media account, you acknowledge and agree that you may only do so pursuant to each site’s terms and policies. 

If you primarily use our Services to assist third parties with their social media management projects from within the European Union (“EU”), we will process any data received from you as a data processor on your behalf. Under EU law, you are categorized as a data controller of your client’s data and are responsible for complying with certain data protection laws. Please contact Loomly.com if you wish to supplement our policies to adhere to your data security requirements. 

If you have hired an individual or business to assist you with your social media management projects, and that individual or business uses Loomly.com as a tool, we may be processing your personal data on behalf of our customers and must do so in accordance with their instructions. This means that if you wish to access any personal data we process on behalf of a Loomly.com customer and request that we correct, amend, or delete such information, you should contact that Loomly.com customer with your request. We will then help them to fulfill that request in accordance with their instructions. 

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service. 

In accordance with applicable privacy law, you have the following rights in respect of your Personal Information that we hold: 

  * Right of access and portability. The right to obtain access to your Personal Information along with certain information, and to receive that Personal Information in a commonly used format and to have it ported to another data controller. 
  * Right to rectification. The right to obtain rectification of your personal information without undue delay where that personal information is inaccurate or incomplete. 
  * Right to erasure. The right to obtain the erasure of your Personal Information without undue delay in certain circumstances, such as where the Personal Information is no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which it was collected or processed. 
  * Right to restriction. The right to obtain the restriction of the processing undertaken by us on your Personal Information in certain circumstances, such as where the accuracy of the Personal Information is contested by you, for a period enabling us to verify the accuracy of that Personal Information. 
  * Right to object. The right to object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, to the processing of your Personal Information, and to object to processing of your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes, to the extent it is related to such direct marketing. 

If you wish to exercise one of these rights, please [contact us](mailto:contact@loomly.com). Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct or request deletion of your personal information by logging into your account, or by contacting us. We will respond to your request within 30 days. 

If Calendy, Inc is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred as a business asset. In such cases, we will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred and/or becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy. 

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. 

However, please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and we are unable to guarantee the absolute security of the Personal Information we have collected from you. 

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. 

If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to United States and process it there. 

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third-party's site. It is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. 

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites or services. 

Only persons age 18 or older have permission to access our Service. Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children"). 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you learn that your Children have provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 24, 2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. 

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. 

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:contact@loomly.com).
